http://www.lifetips.com/about/privacy.html

Privacy Statement
We care about protecting your privacy, especially the privacy of children under the age of 13.
We will not rent, sell or give away your e-mail address to any marketer or spammer. You will not wind up on any spam list by signing-up for a lifetips.com newsletter. Guaranteed.
We do not provide advertisers with access to any information that would allow them to target you specifically.
We'll always allow you to cancel your subscription.
If you are under 13, you should not sign-up for any lifetips.com newsletters unless authorized by a responsible adult.
This notice is to inform you about the policies for collection
and use of personally identifiable information at lifetips.com.
Sites which are linked to our site may have different policies;
please review the privacy policy notices on those sites for details.
1. Your privacy will be protected. We do not collect personally
identifiable information (name and email address) about you on
this site without your knowledge, and all such information is
collected directly from you. You are not required to provide us
with this information, but if you choose not to, you may not be
able to participate in some of the activities on this site.
2. Personally Identifiable Information: If you choose to sign
up for the lifetips service to gain additional functionality,
we may ask you to provide the following information: name, email
address, zip code, age, gender and country. We will NOT disclose,
sell or exchange your personally identifiable information to or
with anyone, without your specific permission, except when we
believe disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with
the law or legal process; (2) protect or defend the rights or
property of lifetips or others; (3) enforce this Agreement; or
(4) respond to claims that the contents of any communications
violate the rights of others.
3. Aggregated User Information That Does Not Identify Any User
Individually: We perform statistical analyses of the collective
characteristics and behavior of our members and visitors, to measure
overall demographics and interests regarding specific areas of
the lifetips domain and to analyze how and where to use our resources.
We also use the aggregate data collected to inform our sponsors
as to the number of people who have seen and "clicked" on their
advertisement. In addition, lifetips may compile and disclose
aggregate information about its users for promotional or other
purposes. For example, we might want to disclose that a certain
percentage of our users are located within a particular geographic
area or fall within a particular age range.
4. Lifetips.com does not share member information with third
parties without permission. During the registration process, members
may grant permission for Lifetips.com to share contact information
with third parties or sponsors. The option for granting this permission
is clearly marked on the registration pages.
5. You will not be spammed. At Lifetips.com we do not endorse
the practice of sending unsolicited commercial e-mail (spam).
When you become a Lifetips.com member, you will receive Lifetips
e-mails on the topics you have requested and an occasional update
from our president, Byron White.
6. You can terminate your membership at any time. If you wish
to unsubscribe, just log on to your MyLifetips account and click
on the trash can for each newsletter you wish to unsubscribe from.
To request that we not share your personal information with
third parties (in cases where you previously granted us permission
to share such information - we do not share your personal information
with third parties without your permission), you can call our office
at 617-227-8800.
The request will be honored as soon as we receive it, but does
not affect any information which you provided to us and which
we shared with third parties with your consent prior to our receipt
of such request.
To request that we not share your personal information with
sponsors (in cases where you previously granted us permission
to share such information - we do not share your personal information
with sponsors without your permission), you can call our office
at 617-227-8800.
The request will be honored as soon as we receive it, but does
not affect any information which you provided to us and which
we shared with sponsors with your consent prior to our receipt
of such request.
To have all of your personal information removed from our database,
you can call our office at 617-227-8800.
At the current time, we are not able to offer users the direct
ability to delete their personal information from our database,
but we will be happy to delete such information after we receive
a request to that effect.
7. We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal
preferences when you visit our site.
This could include only
showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login
to some of our features.
We also use third party advertisements on lifetips.com to support our
site.
Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies
and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send
these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program)
information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you
used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash
installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes
(showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for
example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited
(such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or
third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing
preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
However, this can affect how you are able to interact with
our site as well as other websites.
This could include the
inability to login to services or programs, such as logging
into forums or accounts.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices
of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
LifeTips.com
205 Portland St
Suite 500
Boston, MA 02114
617-227-8800
Welcome Readers
Enjoy thousands of free tips that make your life better, smarter and more fun!
Welcome Listeners
Listen to more than 300 podcasts with industry experts that share tips and advice.
Privacy Policy and Unsubscribe
LifeTips Site Map
Guru Login
Ever wonder how you could make your life better and more fun? So have tens of millions of fans who have turned to LifeTips for answers over the past decade. We keep the tips, advice, books, podcasts and writing services flowing, so you can keep your life and business growing in the right direction. Upward!
© 2020 LifeTips
— All rights reserved.
